Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Episode 18
Eun Jo.
𝘞𝘩𝘢𝘵 𝘪𝘴 𝘩𝘢𝘱𝘱𝘦𝘯𝘪𝘯𝘨?
𝘛𝘩𝘢𝘵 𝘱𝘦𝘳𝘴𝘰𝘯 𝘪𝘴 𝘤𝘳𝘢𝘻𝘺.
𝘞𝘩𝘺 𝘪𝘴 𝘩𝘦 𝘤𝘢𝘭𝘭𝘪𝘯𝘨 𝘮𝘦 𝘭𝘪𝘬𝘦 𝘵𝘩𝘢𝘵?
Come over here.
Did he forgot the sins he committed?
Why is he calling me like that?
No matter how many times I call you,
Seems like you won't come to me again.
Then, I'll have to go to you.
Whenever I start talking to you...
I've never been able to finish what I started saying to you.
Since before I'm done talking, you always turn and walk away so quickly.
That's a very bad habit you have.
Things to say to MMM
If you dare move a step before I'm done saying all these things I wrote on this list...
you'll get scolded by me you brat, all right?
1. No matter what happens, don't be alarmed.
-What are you sa-
-Whatever happens, don't be surprised.
I'll take care of all of it.
What happened?
2. And believe that Dae Seong True Winemakers will be safe.
If you endure this well,
And even if an earthquake occurs, you won't be shaken.
What in the world are you sa-
3.
Something happened to the winery while I was gone, right?
Don't hesitate, but say it quickly.
3. You keep your mouth shut.
What in the world is thi-
Don't even let out a peep.
Do not cry.
Do not even scream.
Just like when you had a piece of glass stuck in your knee, but you didn't make a sound.
Of course, I didn't really like what you did back then but...
Just this one time, do that for me,
or it'll be hard for me.
You won't tell me straight out?
As far as number 4...
When everything is over,
and I can still see your face at that time...
I will tell you then.
Keep that note safe. It's very important.
What are you doing right now?
Are you joking now?
What is this about? What are you saying is going to happen?
What's going to happen is not important, but what's important is that
this will all ultimately pass..
That it will all be taken care of, like nothing ever happened.
You just have to know that.
Grandfather.
Ahjussi Dang Sook.
Grandmother.
So are you now saying without discussing it with us,
that you went along and decided for yourselves?
That isn't the case, right?
I heard wrong, right?
Of course, you have shareholder's rights to Dae Seong True Winemakers.
So you have the right to make a decision on this...
I know you do and I understand all that but...
𝘞𝘩𝘢𝘵𝘦𝘷𝘦𝘳 𝘩𝘢𝘱𝘱𝘦𝘯𝘴, 𝘥𝘰𝘯'𝘵 𝘣𝘦 𝘢𝘭𝘢𝘳𝘮𝘦𝘥.
Believe that Dae Seong True Winemakers will be safe.
But still the winery...
Dad...
What I mean is... This winery is not just any ordinary winery...
It's Dae Seong True Winemakers.
Dae Seong True Winemakers must remain Dae Seong True Winemakers forever.
Passing it on to someone else's hands... That...
Hyo Seon.
Yes.
Yes, Grandpa.
Let's begin the process quickly.
Anyway, we can't afford to leave it to young guys like you forever.
By doing this, we judged that t wouldn't cause any financial loss to you guys either.
Grandfather, this isn't about any loss.
How can Dae Seong True Winemakers be handed to someone else?
We understand well what the elders' thoughts are.
Even if Hyo Seon, our mother, and I put our shares together,
I understand well that if the elders are of one mind, we will have to follow.
Unni.
But, elders...
do you know who's fault it was that Dae Seong True Winemakers suddenly started faltering?
It was because of the shameless attacks of Hong Joo Ga,
who you are planning to sell your shares to.
And our...
And our dad wouldn't have collapsed like that if it weren't for them.
When our dad passed away like that, weren't you all sincere in grieving for him, right?
It was a waste.
Didn't you say it was such a waste to have lost him and what you were supposed to do?
Didn't you cry over the fact that we lost the pillar of this family?
I really remember it very clearly.
How did such sincere feelings fade away so quickly?
I also remember so clearly how you told us that the dream our dad couldn't achieve,
we must achieve it at all costs.
How can you make such a decision so lightly without caring for anything else?
If you were really sincere in what you've said to us, you wouldn't do this.
Elders, you can't do this to us.
Child, you are not supposed to talk right now.
Shut your mouth.
Grandmother.
Considering how your mother behaves
how dare you preach to your elders?
Grandmother.
Why are you all like this?
Did I say something wrong?
Does this child have the right to say such things to us?
That's all I'm saying.
Don't talk carelessly about my mom, Grandmother!
Have you ever followed our mom around and seen her bad behaviour?
Do you have any proof? Is there a single person who has seen her?
I've lived with her and I'm telling you that it's not true.
If our mom really did such a thing,
I'm the one who could never forgive her.
I've told you so many times that it wasn't true!
Even if she did that,
Even if there was the odd chance that such a thing happened,
you can't say things like that.
For my younger brother Joon Soo's sake,
you shouldn't do that, Grandmother.
Aigoo. Who knows if that kid is really your younger brother?
Unni.
If he is or not, how can anyone know?
Since we're on the topic
since that person came to our home
think about how much money that person took or threw away outside?
Grandmother!
If that was all true,
what would you do about it?
What did you say?
Even if it's all true, there is nothing you can do to my mother.
You can't bring someone back from the dead to sign the divorce papers.
You don't have the right to remove her from the family registry.
Our mother has nothing to do with this situation.
This, this, this, this... rude child!
How dare you speak like that in front of your elders. Where you're going...
Aigoo... I can't believe I was spoken to like that by a child.
Let's talk for a moment.
The thing I thought I was the only one who knew...
It seems you already knew...
and everyone else did too.
I was the only one
who didn't know that everyone already knew.
Get yourself together. Is that the main problem right now?
Is this the time for you to be like this?
Are you going to give up
our brewery to Hong Joo Ga?
Is that what you're going to do?
I can't. I can't do that.
I'll even go to all the elders one by one and beg them on my knees.
I won't move a single step until they agree to not give it up.
What are you going to do?
What do you want to do?
You're the smart one. I'm telling you to think of something!
Wait. Wait a minute.
Just give me one hour.
No, just give me 30 minutes.
No...just ten minutes!
Let me be alone.
Just ten minutes...alone.
Hey!
You better not break down!
I said you better not break down
and abandon me!
Mom
The phone is off and you're being re-directed to the voice mail system.
Mom.
I'll take on all the punishment,
so don't come back.
Don't ever come back and just hide well.
It's true.
I thought that if we hid and lived on like nothing happened
everything would just go away.
But that's not the case, Mom.
You'll always be a witch until the day you die, Mom.
And I'm the witch's daughter.
I'll burn in hell for you,
so don't ever come back, Mom.
The wine is brewing well, Eun Jo.
Because I'm the witch's daughter, does that make me a witch too?
Is it because I'm a witch that I've been caught under a spell?
It seems I've completely forgotten who this person is
and everything that he's done.
I told you to be ready for anything that may happen.
And I told you to just watch what I'm doing.
Why are you crying?
That's why I really don't want to do anything.
I want to just leave everything in this person's hands
and just sit here and do nothing like these jars here.
♫ It must be you.  ♫
♫ I cannot be without you. ♫
I told you not to be shocked, but you're clearly shocked.
I told you not to make a peep, but you're already crying.
You horrible woman.
I also need to gradually start taking action now.
Do you know that?
I'm also a little scared.
Although I'm scared, I won't hide.
I'll handle things well and come back.
♫ I can't let you go a second time  ♫
♫ I'm saying I can't forget you and live.  ♫
And...the spell on the witch's daughter came to an end.
When that person said he was scared,
I also suddenly started feeling scared.
Stop right there.
What is that you said you're going to do?
Where are you going now? What are you going to do?
I'll be back.
Just do nothing and wait.
Be good and wait for me.
And don't cry.
♫ Can't you hear my voice? ♫
♫ Come to me. ♫
♫ It must be you. ♫
♫ I cannot be without you. ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫ The love I will protect ♫
♫ The love I love
Because for me ♫
♫ Yes, if it's just you, it is enough ♫
How much do we have if we rake out everything we have?
Is there somewhere we can go to find out what and how much we have?
You don't know anything about the status of your assets?
No. How would I know?
That's why I'm looking into it now.
After we find out, let's sell everything.
But this is stuff we already know.
Where can we find out about the information we don't know about?
Financial Supervisory Service
What's the matter?
We have no chance.
No chance?
That's right.
That's what it was.
- What do you mean?
- They were going to buy our brewery
and get rid of it.
What did you say?
Get rid of it? They said they were going to keep our name even if they buy it.
It was a lie.
They were just going to get rid of the brand completely
so that Hong Joo Ga's wine would take over the market.
Also, they said they would fully support me in developing yeast.
Then that would make me a researcher for Hong Joo Ga.
What?
That's what their plan was.
That's right.
Otherwise, there would be no reason for them to give us so much money for Dae Seong True Winemakers' shares.
It didn't make any sense
that they were offering so much more than the market price.
From the beginning, those schemers...
What are you saying?
Explain it to me so I understand.
Let's go first.
There's nothing else we can do other than persuading the elders.
Jeong Woo, let's go.
Complete list of lobbying expenses ("Bribes" to government employees/ politicians)
Complete list of lobbying expenses
Who was it? Who was the person that gave you this absurd information?
There's no need for you to know that.
It's not important either.
So, what are you going to do about it? Let's hear what you're planning to do.
You're obviously here to negotiate,
so let's hear what you want and the details of your negotiation.
Keep your mouth shut, Gi Jeong.
It's not as if I didn't expect it
but I didn't think it would be this bad, Father.
And also Hyung.
This information, it's not our company's.
It isn't?
No, it isn't.
Why would you bring something so shabby and try such sloppy negotiations?
What are you asking for, you punk?
Don't say anything, Gi Jeong. Don't say a word.
If you're asking what I want for this,
doesn't it mean you're acknowledging the content of this material, Hyung?
No.
No. I need to know what you're going to ask for,
so I can agree or make a counteroffer.
Tell me what you want.
Gi Jeong.
You sneaky bastard!
Because you had the most pitiful expression on your face,
there was a moment when I blamed myself for making you suffer too much.
How could you...
You don't know how shocked I was when I saw the amount of tax evasion, Hyung.
That was when I first realized that money can exist in such large amounts in this world.
You are quite skilled.
The way the financial statements were manipulated was just too amazing.
Even someone like me, who studied in America for so long, was atonished.
Who was it?
The legal and accounting team with such great teamwork?
So touching.
Not to mention, even the list of political lobbyists—
Shut your mouth.
If it weren't for these methods, do you think Hong Joo Ga could've grown in such a short time?
By father's ability?
Stop acting so naive and tell me what you want.
This is enough for now.
The request I want to make, you know it already.
Keep your hands off of us.
Us?
Dae Seong True Winemakers. Don't touch us. That's my request.
Would you like to listen how ridiculous that request is, Hyung?
I have to send a urgent message first.
Wait a moment.
[New e-mail received]
Shut your mouth.
If it weren't for these methods, do you think Hong Joo Ga could've grown in such a short time?
By father's ability?
Stop acting so naive.
And tell me what you want.
For today, I just needed you to acknowledge that this material belonged to Hong Joo Ga.
I didn't even have to work on you for too long.
Thanks for admitting it so easily, Hyung.
It's no use, Hyung.
I've already transferred it to somewhere safe.
I'll give you some time.
By tomorrow... If you bought any stocks from the elders, give them all back.
And if there is anything you wanted to buy from them, give up on it quickly.
What are you thinking?
Do you want me to just leave this alone?
I'll do that so please go see to Joon Soo.
Okay.
We only need 2 of the elders on our side.
If we put all our shares together is 40 percent.
We just need another 11 percent.
So who do we need to persuade?
The representative elder...
And the family elder grandmother.
Why Grandmother?
If we can't convince the grandmother, then what happens?
Then we have to convince the other 12 elders.
I'll go see my father's second cousin's grandmother...
So Unni, you meet grandfather.
No.
I'll meet grandmother.
I think that would be better.
Better tomorrow morning than tonight, right?
Eat your dinner.
Please eat your dinner.
Please open the door, Ahjumma! How can you do this, Ahjumma?
How can you do this after my mom abandoned me, Ahjumma?!
Did you encourage her to abandon me?
Please open the door, Ahjumma!
Keep your head down
and continue to live with me.
I told you that was your punishment!
You guys go on ahead first.
I left my cellphone.
I'll be right back.
All you just have to do is do nothing and wait for me.
Wait for me. Like a good girl.
Don't cry.
You just received a new e-mail.
New mail
Sender: Hong Gi Hoon.
To: Dae Seong True Winemakers
This is a message written from Hon Gi Hoon's mobile phone
1 attachment
AudioRecording01. wav
Password required to open file
PW: Dae Seong Do Ga
Re-enter password
Let go of me. Who are you people? Who sent you?
Did Hong Gi Jeong send you?
Spanish History
He hasn't come back yet?
He didn't contact you either?
No.
Okay.
Go sleep.
Wait. Can we talk for a bit?
About what?
Hyo Seon and I—
Just for a little bit.
"Once upon a time, there was a man named Choi Man Jeong"
"who lived in a village with his wife named Jo."
"They lived happily together with two princesses."
"Although there were happy times, there were also sad times."
"His wife fell ill,"
"and passed away."
Joon Soo, is it boring?
Noona will read you a more interesting story, okay?
Come here.
Should I read another one?
Aigoo.
Who knows if that kid is really your brother?
I'll read you this one.
- What did you say?
- I've saved up a bit till now.
If it's not enough, I can even take out a loan.
You're getting married?
Yeah.
Really?
I can just get a place with one room
and a kitchen for now.
Starting from that,
the number of spoons and bowls in the house can grow from there.
Can't I just live like that?
I thought it would be in a few years.
By then, I would be able to do a lot more for you.
But right now, I can't help you with anything.
But...I can't make you wait until I have the ability.
All right.
I'll help you, whether it's a loan or whatever.
Go to sleep.
That's not it. I meant...
I'm afraid if you stay here any longer, you'll get sick.
We probably can't sell everything right away.
We don't know when there will be buyers.
We can put them out for sale, but we can't rely on this.
When will we get the money for the rice wine we sold?
How much do we have? How much do we need?
It's worth quite a lot, but you know...
That's all to be shared with the elders.
I think it'll be better
for me to meet Grandmother.
No, I'll go.
I am so angry at Halmoni for insulting Joon Soo.
You too, right?
Come with me. I want to show you something.
I told you to come.
This is my mom's dress.
Mom...
Our mom now...
When she first came to our house, her clothes got ruined,
so I gave her this to wear.
At that time...
seeing Mom wearing my mom's clothes,
I felt that if I couldn't have her right away,
I would die.
You are really pretty.
Why are you like this?
I don't know.
My tears just kept running down...
Within my desire to have her,
I also already felt the fear of her being taken away from me.
Do you understand?
I wanted to have her,
but at the same time, I was also anxious that she'd be taken away from me anytime.
So I was determined
not to lose her.
This is the bible my mom always read
and the rosary that she prayed with.
Look at this.
This is a photo of Dad when he was young.
He looks exactly like Joon Soo, doesn't he?
If I see your sulking face, I don't think I'd be able to leave.
So I'm leaving like this.
I'll leave alone now,
and in the future, I'll grab your hand tightly
and take you to Ushuaia.
I'll even take you to the moon and stars.
Don't run away somewhere again,
don't go anywhere and just wait at home.
I'll endure everything with the thought of you waiting.
I hope you'll also endure everything with the thought of me returning.
I like you, Eun Jo.
You're my favorite in this whole world.
I love you.
If we had to separate for a while,
I wanted to write this kind of letter to you.
Don't go anywhere and wait for me.
I love you, Eun Jo.
A letter saying all that.
I really wanted to write a letter
that would make your heart flutter and wait for me, but ...
I have to cross a river of no return.
As the coward I am, instead of telling you to wait for me,
I have to ask you to stop me.
Can you stop me?
Eun Jo...a fool just like Hong Gi Hoon
who can't cry even when your knees are bleeding...
If you hold me back, I think I can stop here.
Before I get on the train, grab me, Eun Jo.
My tears couldn't even fall out.
My chest felt so tight thst I couldn't even bresthe.
"If you hold me back, I think I can stop here."
You couldn't stop, so you came all the way here? Is that what you were saying?
♫ Where you can't hold me again  ♫
♫ I ask again about the way.  ♫
♫ Saying I want to see you  ♫
♫ and hold you again ♫
♫ While looking at heaven I'm praying ♫
♫ It must be you. ♫
I'll even take you to the moon and stars.
When?
Can you stop me?
How?
If you hold me back, I think I can stop here.
This person...was clinging onto me like clutching at straws.
Eun Jo...a fool just like Hong Gi Hoon
who can't even cry when your knees are bleeding.
That person's knees were also bleeding...
Can you stop me?
If I had known
a cruel, useless 18 year old brat
was the only person in the world
who could hold back that person,
I also...
wouldn't have had any reason to cry
like a bird calling my own name.
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫ The love I will protect ♫
♫ The love I love
Because for me ♫
♫ Yes, if it's just you, it is enough ♫
♫ because you are the only one I love. ♫
Why did you come so early in the morning?
What's wrong with you?
That person didn't come home?
He didn't.
I can't reach him on the phone.
I couldn't either.
Something must have happened.
What could it be?
He told me he'll be right back so to just wait for him.
If he said he'll come back,
he would have been back by now.
Noona!
Why is his car here?
If his car is here, shouldn't he be here also?
- Jeong Woo. - Yes.
Something happened, right?
Right?
Tell me what's going on. This is really frustrating!
Jeong Woo.
What?
I'm a little anxious right now.
Yes.
Go tell Hyo Seon...
What?
Tell Hyo Seon to go meet with my father's second cousin's grandmother.
And also...
[Re-enter password]
Are you okay?
I'm alright.
No. I'm not alright.
No. I'm fine.
What was the 4th thing he wanted to say?
He said he had 4 things to say to me.
He only told me 3 and said he'll tell me the last one later...
[Things to say to MMM]
PW: MMM
Downloading file
He left earlier.
Where to?
That I don't know...
I heard you haven't eaten anything.
You shouldn't be like that.
You need to eat well.
Go and bring some food for this guy.
I feel bad for having to go this far.
But, I needed some time.
I have no intention to mistreat you at all.
Father and mother's divorce hearing will be tomorrow.
Then a few days after that, there will be a shareholder's meeting.
Between the divorce hearing and the shareholder's meeting,
the Dae Seong brewery issue will be resolved.
You just need to stay here for a few days.
I didn't know you'd resort to the point of being a gangster, Hyung Gi Jeong.
It was Director Park, wasn't it?
The person who sent you the documents.
How could you handle things so carelessly, Hyung?
It is Director Park...
Right?
I also hope what I'm thinking won't happen.
Even if I don't do it, you're already done for.
What did you say?
When I see you resorting to these tactics, I can finally understand.
How weak of a person you are, Hyung.
It'll be over soon, Gi Hoon.
Don't waste your energy and just take care of yourself.
The request I want to make, you know it already.
Keep your hands off of us.
Us?
Dae Seong True Winemakers. Don't touch us.
That's my request.
Would you like to listen how ridiculous that request is, Hyung?
I have to send an urgent message first.
Jeong Woo.
Yes.
That person...
It seems like he's being held by his so-called Hyung.
What did you say?
That person...
he tried to negotiate with Hong Joo Ga's weakness.
I think that information is somewhere inside this computer.
Put the computer in the car, Jeong Woo.
What did you say?
I have to exchange it for him.
What's Hyo Seon doing?
Grandmother.
Until you come out to talk to me...
I won't take a single step out of this spot.
Please?
I have nothing to say to you child, so go home immediately.
Grandmother.
I'll remember what you said about Joon Soo until I die.
Even after you pass away, I won't forget it at all.
I'll hate you, Grandmother!
Because grandmother is like this, my mom can't come back home.
If Mom doesn't come home,
are you going to take care of Joon Soo?
You'll sell Dae Seong True Winemakers to someone else,
and then use that money to send our Joon Soo to study abroad?
After marrying me off, are you going to marry our unni off too?
Are you going to take care of our entire family?
Grandmother!
Grandmother.
Grandmother...
I came to stay here with you.
Noona told me to be with you.
What is Eun Jo doing?
She had to go somewhere.
Where?
I don't know either.
Who can overcome Eun Jo's stubbornness?
Hong Gi Jeong, this is Goo Eun Jo.
You kidnapped Hong Gi Hoon, right?
What are you talking about? Kidnapping?
He's my younger brother.
Have you ever seen an older brother kidnap his younger brother?
I thought you said he wasn't your younger brother.
I definitely heard you say he was not.
Since I'm not as meticulous as Hong Gi Hoon
I didn't even think about recording our past conversation.
But, I definitely remember you saying it.
You said: I only have one brother named, Hong Gi Tae.
Hong Gi Hoon is not my brother.
But he is my father's son.
I can see how you've been treating your half-brother.
Get to the point of what it is you have to say.
If it's about Gi Hoon, I don't know anything.
So we'll just end this call immediately.
Release him immediately, Hong Gi Jeong.
I won't listen to you. All you have to do is listen to me.
At first, I left home thinking of exchanging these materials
I have in my car for Hong Gi Hoon.
But if he was someone who was worried about his own safety,
I think he wouldn't have done this in the first place.
If he was a man who was concerned about his own safety a long time ago...
A very long time ago, he wouldn't have asked me to stop him.
I couldn't do anything back then...
So what can I do now?
Those are the thoughts running through my head.
He would not want me to get him out so easily.
Hong Gi Jeong.
I'm in front of the Prosecutor's Office right now.
I plan on getting it all done at once.
I will report all that you did to Dae Seong True Winemakers.
I'm going to hand over these documents and the voice recording
and even reveal Hong Hi Hoon's real identity.
I don't know what's inside these documents,
but just from the audio recording,
even a fool can tell you've done extremely horrible things.
Let's meet and talk in person.
I thought about this a lot,
and I know this the right thing to do.
No matter how many of Dae Seong True Winemakers' stocks you obtain,
Or even so the name of Dae Seong True Winemakers gets erased in our country forever,
this is the right thing to do.
Even our late father would agree that this is the right thing to do.
Look here, Goo Eun Jo.
Look here, Hong Gi Jeong.
But the main reason I'm going to do this is that...
I don't want that person, Hong Gi Hoon,
to be ashamed anymore.
Look here!
That person couldn't come to me because he always felt ashamed.
He never said what he truly felt because he felt too guilty.
And I always said something different than what I felt in my heart.
There was not even once that I said any warm words to that person.
So if I just hand this over to you to get him freed,
he and I will never have a chance.
Hong Gi Jeong...
If the fact that Hong Gi Jeong kidnapped his own younger brother, becomes known somehow...
It can cause you big trouble.
I will give you some time before I get into that building...
so please release him.
And let him call me.
Then I won't need to go in there
to tell them that you kidnapped your younger brother.
Goodbye.
Make a call to Lawyer Kim.
Incoming call
Hello?
Roll your window down a bit so that I can see your face.
Who told you to do this?
Are you okay?
Don't you see it?
I'm fine.
That's enough. Go home.
You can't.
You can't take those files and do what you're thinking.
It's the only way to save Dae Seong Do Ga.
♫  I'm secretly smiling  ♫
♫  Love leaves again this way  ♫
What are you doing?
I asked what you are doing?!
♫  In the sadness you left in the longing  ♫
♫  I walk this street again  ♫
♫  I am living day after day  ♫
Eun Jo!
♫  In your name when tears appear  ♫
♫  I can't bear it  ♫
♫  So I can't laugh  ♫
♫  I call out your name again.  ♫
♫  It must be you  ♫
♫  I cannot be without you  ♫
♫  Like this for another day, month or year  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if I am hurt  ♫
♫  I don't mind even if my heart breaks  ♫
♫  because, yes, you are the only one I love.  ♫
♫  I'm saying I can't let you go a second time  ♫